We are Jyosho TV!
What are we going to do today?
We are going to do a hidden camera!
It's our first time to do a hidden
camera!
Please look forward to it!
I can't see it!
Wow!
It's a real one!
I'll wear this and dance!
We'll dance to Kisendon desu ki!
I didn't think we'd be dancing to this.
I was thinking about doing the dance
version, but I didn't think we'd be
doing it.
I'm not sure if I'll be able to do it.
This is my first time doing a song like
this.
We'll do our best!
This program is a program where six
members who are active to promote
something for the first time challenge
various things and promote the world's
exciting ball makers!
We'll prove it! Happy New Day!
The first day of the shoot.
The girls are getting ready for the
shoot.
Let's do our best!
It's amazing how dark it is.
The girls are getting ready for the
shoot.
I'm not sure.
I don't know.
You're not sure, Koyo-chan.
I'm not sure.
Shall we start?
Yes.
Please.
All right.
I'm not sure.
Music, start!
I'm scared!
Aki-chan!
I can't do this!
I'm scared!
Do not look at me!
Go!
No.
Can I send it?
No, don't choose.
I'm scared!
I'm sorry.
Who is it?
Where is it?
I want to show you.
I'm sorry.
The dance is getting more and more
difficult.
I can't do it anymore.
What should I do?
There is no one here.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm in the center.
What should I do?
I'm scared!
What is this?
I'm gonna die!
I'm scared!
Please subscribe to our channel!
I'm going to do it again!
Where are you going?
I'm going to kill you!
I can't feel the real thing.
I can't do this.
Like Like Like Like...
OH MY!
Thats no good!
Waaha
Turn it on!
Kizi Kizi Kizi Kitchen
Spicy honey
Horror game with Alien
I'm scared.
Who is there?
I don't know.
Someone is moving.
I'm scared.
Sanamii!
Watch until the end!
Where is she?
Open the door!
What?
I'm scared!
It's the center!
I was looking at the center!
Where did you go?
Who said the song?
I don't know.
Let's take a look.
It's been a while.
Aki-chan?
I can't hear anything.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Nobody is here.
I can hear the number.
I can't hear it.
I can't hear anything.
It's like making an arch.
It's totally different.
Is it just me?
Wow.
It's totally different from me.
It's the center.
It's close.
I'm not moving at all.
Kokotoko is making her center turn of
the choreography.
N30i is making me turn sideways.
Where you in there, Tsuji?
Look at Manami.
Rio was such a cool girl capacidad and
it's crazy
That holeốn
Huh still
sorte
K sesame
Why don't you move?!
Oops!
Flinch
To Be Continued
I'm not alone.
I'm surrounded by people.
I'm not sure if I'm doing it right.
I'm not sure.
I'm not a bad person.
They are facing each other.
Why are they meeting?
They are amazing.
I'm scared.
You are a間違いだ。
It was fun.
It was a big kiss.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you.
Bye bye.
Please subscribe to my channel!
It's your fault that my heart is
pounding
I'll become even cuter tomorrow
Oh, please look at me at any time
My precious feelings
I'm thrilled, I'm excited
Thank you, my days of excitement
I don't even know the end of my dreams
From now on, it's a one-way end
I can't forget this moment
I'm so happy
Because I fell in love with you
Let's go!
My feelings are fluttering
Love will eventually turn into love
It's complicated, but it's simple
Happiness
My heart is being filled
I want more
Let's go!
The Magic Washer
I'm sure you can follow the magic.
Please like and subscribe!
I can say it now, I don't even hesitate
to shed tears
I remember the time we met
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, I'll go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, I ring
the bell of the rainbow
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, I cry my
tears
I wear a rainbow dress